## **Andrew Trumenov**

## Middle web developer (Full-Stack)

Preferred Ruby on Rails + MariaDB/MySQL



Middle web developer with 10+ years of experience in backend and full-stack development. Focused on Ruby on Rails with MariaDB, experienced in DevOps tasks (Docker, Nginx, Capistrano). Comfortable in legacy and modern stacks. Highly motivated and always eager to improve both code and processes.

Education:	
School, Krihiy Rih, Ukraine	1993-2003
Kryvyi Rih National University (KNU), Ukraine Bachelor's Degree in Automated Systems	2010-2014
Experience:	
Civil builder, <b>freelance</b> (elance, upwork). Stack: Pascal (Delphi7, Kylix, Lazarus), C++ (C+builder6, Arduino), PHP, C#, Perl. Achievements: Patch for OpenTracker: auto switch between few sim-cards. Patch for Marlin 3D printer firmware: adaptation of bed position.	2003-2014
<b>Team vint.com.ua</b> (istat24.com) Position: Middle web developer (fullstack). <b>istat24.com</b> : analytics platform (SIP, Call Tracking). Stack: Rails, PostgreSQL, MariaDB, Nginx, AWS, Bootstrap. Achievement: Split 380GB PostgresDB into 2_000+ small Maria DBs – performance increase x100-150 times.	2014-2022
vint.com.ua, patisson-toys.com.ua, pacman.com.ua: shops. Stack: Perl, Crystal-lang, MariaDB, Nginx, Bootstrap. Achievement: MariaDBs master-slave replication. test.vint.com.ua: new frontend for vint.com.ua. Stack: MariaDB, Crystal-lang, Nginx, JQuery.	
svc-power.com.ua: shop. Stack: MariaDB, PHP, Codeigniter4, JQuery.	
Team testomat.io  Position: Middle web developer (fullstack).  app.testomat.io: Test management system.  Stack: Rails, MariaDB/MySQL5.7 + Clickhouse, Meilisearch, TailwindCSS, Ember.js, Jira plugin (React.js).  Achievement: cookie authorization for Testomat Jira plugin.	2022-now
	School, Krihiy Rih, Ukraine Kryvyi Rih National University (KNU), Ukraine Bachelor's Degree in Automated Systems  Experience:  Civil builder, freelance (elance, upwork). Stack: Pascal (Delphi7, Kylix, Lazarus), C++ (C+builder6, Arduino), PHP, C#, Perl. Achievements: Patch for OpenTracker: auto switch between few sim-cards. Patch for Marlin 3D printer firmware: adaptation of bed position.  Team vint.com.ua (istat24.com) Position: Middle web developer (fullstack). istat24.com: analytics platform (SIP, Call Tracking). Stack: Rails, PostgreSQL, MariaDB, Nginx, AWS, Bootstrap. Achievement: Split 380GB PostgresDB into 2_000+ small Maria DBs – performance increase x100-150 times. vint.com.ua, patisson-toys.com.ua, pacman.com.ua: shops. Stack: Perl, Crystal-lang, MariaDB, Nginx, Bootstrap. Achievement: MariaDBs master-slave replication. test.vint.com.ua: new frontend for vint.com.ua. Stack: MariaDB, Crystal-lang, Nginx, JQuery. svc-power.com.ua: shop. Stack: MariaDB, PHP, Codeigniter4, JQuery.  Team testomat.io Position: Middle web developer (fullstack). app.testomat.io: Test management system. Stack: Rails, MariaDB/MySQL5.7 + Clickhouse, Meilisearch, TailwindCSS, Ember.js, Jira plugin (React.js).

**Contact info**: phone: +380681765917 (viber), telegram: @AndrewTrumenov,

site: trumenov.top, email: <a href="mailto:andrew.trumenov@gmail.com">andrew.trumenov@gmail.com</a>.

**Personal info:** date of birth: 10.04.1987 (38 years), have a car, 3 children, from 2022 - single.

My **daily soft**: Linux Mint, Ubuntu Server, Sublime, Google Chrome, Double Commander, Midnight Commander, phpmyadmin, Tilix, Lazygit, TelegramWeb, realsync, OpenVPN.

**Hobby**: C++ MCU programming (STM32, Arduino), monowheel (Ninebot E+), anime (romcoms), AI. **AI**: Ollama+OpenWebUI+SearxNG at home for fun, I tried Cursor, WindSurf, OpenManus. Always use deepseek, chatgpt.